churpchurp.com 2011-06-16

# ChurpChurp | A Community for Social Media Influencers » Policy

## Privacy Policy

Netcentric Sdn Bhd, operator of the Churpchurp.com website, ("Churpchurp.com") provides an online advertising sale and display service for publishers of Twitter and Facebook Micro-blogs (the "Service"). We sell "Advertiser(s)" the right to place advertisements ("Ad(s)") via the Service on one or more Twitter and Facebook accounts of our network of Micro-blog publishers ("Publisher(s)") and managed by such Publishers. The Service runs on software developed by Netcentric Sdn Bhd, its subsidiaries and third party contractors.

#### A. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

If you are an Advertiser or a Publisher, during your dealings with Churpchurp.com, Churpchurp.com may request any information related to your Twitter and Facebook account and your use of Churpchurp.com’s ads. If you provide such information to Churpchurp.com, Churpchurp.com may collect and store such personal information. Churpchurp.com may collect your email addresses, mailing and billing address, IP address, information about your Twitter and Facebook account, including but not limited to your Twitter followers and Facebook Friends/ Fans. Churpchurp.com will collect information regarding your activities through the Service. Churpchurp.com will collect any comments you may send to Churpchurp.com and any information you may post to the Churpchurp.com site or a Publisher site. Churpchurp.com may also collect information through the use of Cookies (as defined below). Churpchurp.com collects personal information when you: (1) register with Churpchurp.com to become a Publisher or Advertiser, (2) provide comments or submit a problem to Churpchurp.com or a Churpchurp.com Publisher, (3) request information from Churpchurp.com and provide your name or return contact information, or (4) respond to special offers, contests or surveys. As part of the registration process, you may be asked to provide contact information and other personally identifying information.

#### B. COOKIES

"Cookies" are data files that may be downloaded to your computer when you visit the Churpchurp.com site or a Publisher site and permit the Churpchurp.com server to identify your browser whenever you interact with the Churpchurp.com site or a Churpchurp.com Publisher site. Churpchurp.com uses cookies to recognize repeat visits by users of its Service and to collect information about its users’ interactions with the Services. These cookies contain identification information that enables us to streamline your experiences using the Services and to report such information to Publishers and Advertisers. You may set your browser software to reject cookies, but you may not be able to optimize the features of the Services. In some cases, you may not be able to access Services if cookies are disabled.

#### C. EXTERNAL LINKS

As a part of the Services, Churpchurp.com provides links to web sites operated by third parties. Churpchurp.com is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices or the content of those third party sites.

#### D. USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

1\. If you are a Publisher, we may share information about your Twitter and Facebook account, including but not limited to Twitter followers and Facebook Fans / Friends with Advertisers, Publishers or Users. We may share your e-mail address with other Publishers and Twitter followers and Facebook Friends/ Fans who enrolled you into using the Service.

2\. If you are an Advertiser, we may disclosure your contact information and e-mail address to Publishers on whose Sites you have ordered advertisements.

3\. If you are a User, we may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information about you with Publishers or Advertisers such as the number of users who visit a Publisher site or the number of users who clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually. Further, you are encouraged to review the privacy policies of the Publishers that you access. You should contact Publishers directly and review their privacy policies should you have questions concerning their use of your information.

4\. Other Disclosures. Churpchurp.com may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or if Churpchurp.com has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to protect and/or defend the rights and interests of Churpchurp.com. Churpchurp.com may, as permitted by applicable law, disclose your personally identifiable information to Publishers or Advertisers, or third parties in connection with an investigation of fraud, infringement, piracy or other unlawful activity and you expressly authorize Churpchurp.com to make such disclosures.

5\. Domestic and International Use. All personally identifying information collected by Churpchurp.com may be used in Singapore, Malaysia, Australia and Philippines or if the Services are undertaken by Churpchurp.com for a foreign Publisher or Advertiser, such information may be transferred to that Publisher or Advertiser outside of Singapore, Malaysia, Australia and Philippines and you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

6\. Merger or Acquisition. If Netcentric Sdn Bhd is merged or acquired by another entity, personally identifiable information may be transferred to such entity as a part of the merger or acquisition.

#### E. REVIEW AND MODIFICATIONS TO YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION.

If you are a Publisher or Advertiser, you may add, modify or update your email address, name, mailing address and other contact information by accessing the "My Account" page on the Service. It is your responsibility to ensure that the information you have on Churpchurp.com is the most up-to-date information as possible. Churpchurp.com may retain transactional history in order to document a transaction you may have had with a Churpchurp.com Publisher or Advertiser. You should contact the Publisher or Advertiser directly in order to access, modify or update your personal information with them.

#### F. SECURITY

Churpchurp.com stores all information including personally identifiable information obtained through registration securely and considers it part of the assets of its business. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, Churpchurp.com has put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information it collects online. However, data security is a constantly evolving art and science. You should consider any communication that you transmit to Churpchurp.com (such as data, questions or answers, comments, or suggestions) as non-confidential, and agree that Churpchurp.com will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to you is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient.
